I tried using Nano Banana Pro AI to make
an Amazon listing for this face wash
product and got this disappointing
result. At first, it looks not so bad
until you look a little closer. AI
gibberish. But I didn't give up. In
fact, with a little tweaking, I ended up
with a perfect image ready to upload to
the Amazon listing. All from a crappy
photo I took with my phone. Pretty
incredible. Nano Banana Pro is Google's
new AI image generation model, and it
holds the impressive title of being the
only AI able to generate entire Amazon
listing image sets indistinguishable
from professional product photography
and design and all just with your phone
camera and an app on your phone. But
it's not always totally straightforward
to get a good result. In my case, I was
dealing with a tougher product with a
label on it that had a lot of tiny text.
So, there is a trick to this. Since Nano
Banana Pro came out, my team and I have
already used this AI model to generate
hundreds of Amazon listing images. And
there are five key tricks that you can
use to get the most out of NanoBanana
Pro and end up with a listing image set
that you can actually be proud of and
ready to post that's indistinguishable
from professional product photography
and design. And I'm going to walk
through all five of those with you right
now. One of them is the one that I used
to fix the issue that I talked about
earlier on. Now, some of these tricks I
haven't read anywhere else online. I
just discovered them by actually using
it. And if I hadn't discovered them, I
would have thought that this tool was
useless for certain types of products,
like products with a lot of parts or
products with labels on them. But after
discovering these tricks, it actually
allowed me to use Nano Banana Pro on
almost any product to come up with
professional product graphics and
images. Later on in this video, I'm also
going to give you access to a full
ultimate guide for how to use Nano
Banana Pro for product photography
images and graphics. You can download it
for free. First of all, before I get to
those five tips, how to use Nanabanana
Pro. So, to use Nanobanana Pro, you just
download the Gemini app on your phone.
It's a Google app. And then load up the
app and switch from fast mode to
thinking mode. Once you see thinking in
your chatbar, then you'll know that
you're in the right mode. Once you're in
thinking mode, now you can upload photos
from your phone or take photos directly
from the app of products and then pair
that with a prompt to get a professional
product photo or a lifestyle image or a
graphic or anything else you need for
your e-commerce listing. All right, so
now that we're all on the same page,
let's get into these five tips. The
number one tip is take photos from
different angles and different zoom
distances of the product to give the
model enough context to be able to
properly render it. In all the sellers
I've worked with so far on helping them
to use Nano Banana Pro for their Amazon
listings, this is the one thing that I
see everyone get wrong. Everyone's
focused on the prompt and the structure
of the wording of the prompt, but what's
more important is giving the model the
right visual references. So you can see
in this example where I was doing an
Amazon listing for this diffuser, I made
sure to get a zoomin picture of the
buttons on the diffuser because they
have small engravings on them and I
wanted to make sure that the model got
that right. And you could see in the
rendered image that it ended up giving
me for my primary image. If you zoom in,
it did get the buttons right, including
the very specific small engravings on
the button. And the only reason it was
able to do that is because I gave it the
proper context by giving it zoom shots
of the product really close up and at
different angles. So, especially if your
product has multiple parts to it or it
has very fine detail, you need to make
sure to upload enough photos so that the
model has all of the fine detail and
reference images that it needs to be
able to get the product right. In this
case, I was trying to render the primary
image of a more complex product that has
electronics to it. has charge ports. It
has different parts and has a hose and a
body. So, I made sure to give the model
multiple different images close up and
far away so that it understood the
context of the product before rendering
this primary image. The second big tip
for getting good images out of Nano
Banana Pro is if you have a label on the
product, a lot of times, especially if
there's a lot of small text on the
label, the model is going to turn to AI
gibberish on the label. it's not going
to actually show the text. Sometimes it
will get it right, but sometimes it'll
get part of it right and then it'll go
wrong. Like in this example where it
looks good from afar, but if you zoom
in, you actually see that the text is
just AI gibberish. Now, if that happens,
what you need to do is upload a
reference image for the model that zooms
in on that part of the label that it got
wrong and gives it a very clear image of
the text on that label and then tell it
to correct it like I did in this prompt.
A lot of products have labels and a lot
of brand owners that have labels that
have text on their products give up on
using AI because they get AI gibberish.
This is the way around it. You have to
upload separate images of that text.
very clear. Even if you have to take the
label off and show it on a flat surface,
that can work really well, especially if
you're very clear about the prompt that
you use for the AI to have the model fix
the gibberish in the text that it
generated in your initial image. Okay,
the next point is one of the ones that
I've never seen anywhere else, and I
just discovered this on my own by using
the app by accident. And this is a huge,
huge tip. Like without this tip, a lot
of the product images that I've
generated, I wouldn't have been able to
generate cuz I would have given up on
them too early. And that is the image is
different when you download it. Gemini
actually adds another layer of
processing when you click download on
the image. And the downloaded image that
you get is actually different than the
image that you see in the chat. So, in
the example that I was sharing before
where I had this little text on my label
that wasn't looking clear, I actually
did the corrective prompt and it sent me
back one that looked better, but when I
zoomed in in the chat, the image still
didn't look super clear and the text
still looked like gibberish. But then I
downloaded the image and I zoomed in
once I had the full res downloaded image
and it actually had been correct. It's
just that it need that extra layer of
process that Gemini applies to these
images once you download it. So,
especially with products that have text
on them or labels with text on them, I
recommend that you guys download the
image first to see what it looks like
downloaded on your phone or on your
desktop before you judge whether or not
it's ready for you to post. Okay. The
fourth tip is don't try to make too many
changes at once. When you're going back
and forth with Gemini in the app in
chat, you don't want to say, "Hey,
change it from her right hand to her
left hand and change the color from blue
to orange." Also, make sure that the
product is a little bigger. It's going
to mess it up. So, try one change at a
time and then if it starts to go off the
rails, then you can backtrack and you
can correct it one at a time. But if you
try to do a bunch of changes at once,
it's not necessarily going to get
everything right. And sometimes the chat
can go totally off the rails and you
have to abandon the chat altogether.
Now, I'm only scratching the surface
here. If you want a full guide on using
NanoBanana Pro for product photography
and product graphics for Amazon listings
and e-commerce listings, click the first
link in the description of this video
and you can download our ultimate guide
for Nano Banana Pro for Amazon sellers
for free. So, click the link in the
description of this video and you can
get that right now. Which leads me to my
fifth tip, which is abandon chat. A lot
of times you just have to abandon the
chat. And sometimes what I do, a lot of
times what I'll do is I'll just download
the most recent good image before the
chat went off the rails. Like in this
case where I was chatting back and forth
with the AI to try to change things and
it ended up doing some freaky stuff.
Like it turned the product black which
kind of freaked me out and I was like
whoa. Okay, now we're I didn't say
anything about turning the product
product black. Now we're going way off
the rails. I just went back in time,
downloaded an image, re-uploaded that
image to a new chat, and started with
new prompts, and I ended up getting the
result that I wanted, as you can see
here. So, if your chat starts to go off
the rails, all you have to do is just
close down the chat, click new chat,
upload the most recent image that was
good or on the right track, and then
start prompting again. You can also
start brand fresh, brand new by
uploading the same original reference
images that you had of the product in a
new chat and just starting fresh.
Sometimes even the same prompts, same
images will come up with a different
result. So sometimes you just need to
try again. And sometimes you're going to
get it on the first try, but sometimes
you're going to have to go back and
forth quite a bit or start a few chats
until you get one that you like. I'm
really excited to see where all of this
goes. I'm going to be uploading more
videos on this topic because this is the
first time in history. I've been on
Amazon for 10 years that I've seen a
tool like this that had such disruption
in the marketplace. Now, the same tools
that big 9 figureure sellers are using
to create their images are the very same
tools that every small and medium-sized
seller has access to as well. So, it
just completely leveled the playing
field. Anybody can create super high
professional, high converting, high
click-through rate images for their
Amazon product listings anytime with the
Gemini app. So, keep an eye out. I'm
going to be doing more videos on this
topic. And I do a deep dive of creating
an entire listing with Nano Banana Pro
in this video here. So, if you want to
go deeper into this topic, check out
that video now. And I'll see you over
there.